Viewers,
wherever you are,
whatever position you are in.
Are you on the
sickbed?
Whatever medium you are using
to view us,
Once you are under
the influence of this voice,
begin to release yourself , in the name of
Jesus! (Crowd – Amen )
You are created to
lead! Begin to
lead in the name of Jesus!
(Crowd – Amen )
In every area of your life
Begin to lead in the name of Jesus!
(Crowd – Amen )
You are created to lead!
Begin to lead in
the name of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen )
Begin to lead in the name
of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen )
Begin to lead in the name of Jesus!
(Crowd – Amen ), Greater is
He! ( Crowd- Greater is He)
Greater is He! ( Crowd- Greater is He)
It is not less is
He, It is
Greater is He! This is why I
command the spirit of a Leader!
You will lead others ,
in the name of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen)
Begin to lead others in
the name of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen)
In your business begin to lead
others, in the name of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen)
In your finances begin to
lead others in the name of Jesus!
(Crowd – Amen)
In your career begin to lead others in the name
of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen)
Lead in the name of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen)
Lead in the name of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen). Right now
begin to confess your freedom,
your
triumph! Confess your
triumph,
Confess your victory,
Viewers your
health,
be restored, in
the name of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen)
If there is anywhere,
any area, any faculty
or any organ,
that is sick,
Be healed in the name of Jesus!
(Crowd – Amen) Be it
your kidney, (Crowd – Amen)
be it your blood, (Crowd – Amen)
be it your liver, (Crowd – Amen)
be it your heart, (Crowd – Amen)
every organ-
be healed! (Crowd – Amen)
Be restored! (Crowd – Amen)
By the power of the Holy
Ghost, by the blood
of Jesus! (Crowd – Amen)
Holy Ghost! (Crowd - Fire)
Rejoice!
We believe you,
have been inspired by the clip,
you have just watched,
Click here to subscribe;
to witness more of God's power,
at work in our generation
today.And stay up-to
date, with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, service
and testimonies from, "The Synagogue,
Church of All Nations."
Emmanuel TV,
Changing Lives, Changing Nations
and Changing the World!